Guide to the Centro de Accion Social Autonomo Papers, 1963-1978
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES III: SUBJECT AND ORGANIZATIONAL FILES, 1963-1979
  - Subseries I: Protest and Political Movements (United States)
    - Coalition for Economic Survival, 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Communist League, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Farm Labor Organizing Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1976-1981 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous unions, 1971-1978 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression, 1975-1978 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case, 1973-1977 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Native American organizations, 1972-1978 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Native Americans, Skyhorse-Mohawk Defense Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Native Americans, Wasichu, The Continuing Indian Wars, draft, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - New American Movement, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - People's Alliance, National Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Political repression, political prisoners, 1971-1978 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - San Quentin Six, ca. 1975 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Senate Bill One-revision of the Federal criminal code, 1975-1977 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Socialist parties, 1970-1977 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Solar Company, Campbell-San Diego Marine Strikes, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Teamsters Union, 1975-1977 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Texas Farm Workers Union, 1974-1976 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - United Farm Workers Union, 1969-1977 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Subseries J: Protest and Political Movements (International)
    - Chile, 1973-1978 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Cuba, 1960-1977 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Cuba, 11th World Youth Festival, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Cuba, Venceremos Brigade, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Ethiopia-Somalia Conflict, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Iranian Students Association, 1973-1977 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Latin American solidarity movements, 1975-1978 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Mexican Communist Party, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Mexico, social protest, 1972-1977 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Mexico, socialist movements, 1974-1977 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Middle East, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Panama canal, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Puerto Rican Socialist Party, articles, newsletters, 1971-1976 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Puerto Rican Socialist Party, flyers, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Puerto Rican Socialist Party, International Conference in Solidarity with Puerto Rican Independence, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Puerto Rican Socialist Party, manuals for operations, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Puerto Rican Socialist Party, movement to free the five Puerto Rican nationalists, 1975-1977 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Puerto Rican Socialist Party, position papers and reports, 1971-1973 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Puerto Rican Socialist Party, position papers and reports, 1974-1977 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Puerto Rican Socialist Party, position papers and reports, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Puerto Rican Socialist Party, position papers and reports, 1972-1976 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Puerto Rican Socialist Party, position papers and reports, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Ramón Chacón Defense Committee, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Spain, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Universidad Nacional Autónomo de México, strikes, 1972-1977 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Subseries K. Socialist-Political Theory
    - Articles, 1901-1971 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Articles, 1972-1977 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Articles, n.d. (1) (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Articles, n.d. (2) (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Articles, n.d. (3) (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Articles, n.d. (4) (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Articles, n.d. (5) (Box 43, Folder 5)
- SERIES IV: PHOTOGRAPHS, 1973 -1977 AND n.d.
  - Subseries A. Subject
    - Africa (prints) (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Argentina (prints) (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Bakke decision protest (prints) (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Bakke decision protest (negatives) (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - BFI strike, Santa Barbara, (prints) 1976 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Brazil (prints) (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - California Originals Strike (prints) (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Chicago (CASA Local) (prints) (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Chicago (CASA Local) (negatives) (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Chile (prints) (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Coalition Against Repressive Immigration Rally, Washington State, (prints) 1977 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Comite Obrero en Defensa de los Indocumentados en lucha (prints) (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Comite Obrero en Defensa de los Indocumentados en lucha (negatives) (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Conference on Fair Immigration Laws and Practices, East Los Angeles College, (prints) Mar. 8-10, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Coors Beer Boycott (prints) (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Cuba (prints) (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Cuba (negatives) (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Danzos Palomino, Ramon (prints) (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Demonstration at East Los Angeles College, (prints) Apr. 1977 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Demonstration at East Los Angeles College (negatives) (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Demonstrations (1) (prints) (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Demonstrations (2) (prints) (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Demonstrations (3) (negatives) (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Demonstrations (4) (prints) (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Demonstrations (5) (prints) (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Demonstrations (6) (negatives) (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Doris of California (Immigration and Naturalization Service raid) (prints) (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Garcia, Inez (prints) (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Garcia, Inez (negatives) (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Greeley (CASA Local), demonstration, (prints) Sept. 16, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Greeley (CASA Local), (negatives) (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Guatemala (prints) (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Housing (prints) (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Housing (negatives) (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Immigration (prints) (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Immigration (negatives) (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (prints) (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (negatives) (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Industrial Labor (prints) (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Industrial Labor (negatives) (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - International Conference in Solidarity with the Independendence of Puerto Rico, Havana, (prints) Sept. 1975 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - International Worker's Day, Los Angeles, (prints) May 3, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - International Worker's Day, Los Angeles, (negatives) (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Jaramillo, Rubén (prints) (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Jornada de Solidaridad con el Trabajador Mexicano Immigrante en los Estados Unidos, Mexico, (prints) July 19-25, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Land struggles (prints) (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Lebanon (prints) (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Los Tres del Barrio, (1) (prints) (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Los Tres del Barrio,(2) (prints) (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Los Tres del Barrio,(3) (prints) (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Los Tres del Barrio,(4) (negatives) (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Manzo, (prints) 1977 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Manzo, (negatives) (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - March, Bicentennial Without Colonies, Los Angeles, (prints) July 4, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Medina, José Jacques (1) (prints) (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Medina, José Jacques, (negatives) (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Medina, José Jacques, (2) (prints) (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Medina, José Jacques, (3) (negatives) (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Mexican American children (prints) (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Mexican American children (negatives) (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Mexican American women (prints) (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Mexican Presidents Luis Echeverría and José López Portillo (prints) (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Mexican Presidents Luis Echeverría and José López Portillo (negatives) (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Mexico (prints) (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Moratorium Against Deportations of Undocumented Workers, East Los Angeles, Aug. 29, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Native Americans (prints) (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Native Americans (negatives) (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Oakland (CASA) (prints) (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Ortho Mattress Strike (prints) (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Panama (prints) (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - People (prints) (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - People (prints) (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Peoples Republic of China (prints) (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Peru (prints) (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Police brutality (prints) (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Police brutality (negatives) (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Political parties, U.S. (prints) (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Political parties, U.S.(negatives) (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Press conferences (prints) (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Press conferences (negatives) (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Puerto Rico (prints) (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Puerto Rico (negatives) (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Resistencia Rally, Los Angeles, (prints) Aug. 29, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Rodino and Eilberg Bill (prints) (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Rodino and Eilberg Bill (negatives) (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Rodriguez, Antonio (1) (prints) (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Rodriguez, Antonio (2) (prints) (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Rodriguez, Ignacio, Steelworkers Union, Chicago, (prints) Jan. 1977 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Rodriguez, Ignacio, Steelworkers Union, Chicago, (negatives) (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Rodriguez, Jacobo (prints) (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Rodriguez, Jacobo (negatives) (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Sin Fronteras (prints) (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Solidarity with Boulder Six Crusade for Justice, Los Angeles, (prints) Mar. 17, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - South Africa (prints) (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - South Africa (negatives) (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Spain (prints) (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Strikes (prints) (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Strikes (negatives) (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Students (prints) (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Students (negatives) (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Talamante, Olga (prints) (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Teatro Movimiento Primavera (prints) (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Texas farm workers (prints) (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Theatre groups (prints) (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Treviño, Daniel, killing, San Jose (prints) (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - United Farm Workers (prints) (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Viernes de Trabajadores (prints) (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Viernes de Trabajadores (negatives) (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Vietnam (prints) (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Vietnam (negatives) (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Wilmington Ten (prints) (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Women's Conference, California State University Los Angeles (prints) (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - World Trade Union Conference, Cyprus, Mar. 8-11, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Unidentified photographs (1) (prints) (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified photographs (2) (prints) (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified photographs (3) (negatives) (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified photographs (4) (negatives) (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified photographs (5) (color prints) (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified slides (1) (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified slides (2) (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified slides (3) (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified slides (4) (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified slides (5) (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified slides (6) (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified slides (7) (negatives) (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Subseries B: Matted Prints
    - Anti-Franco demonstration, United States (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Children, CASA Bicentennial Without Colonies Demonstration, Los Angeles, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Children in Mexico (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - CLETA Theatre Group, Mexico (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Demonstration against forced sterilization, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Demonstrations (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Farm workers protest in Indiana (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Immigration rights march, East Los Angeles, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Ixtacalco Settlement, Mexico, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Jornada de solidaridad con el Trabajador Mexicano Immigrante en los Estados Unidos, July 1976 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Mexican union demonstration, Nov. 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Police brutality (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Proposition 14, California (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Spicer Corporation Strike, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - La Tolteca Strike, Richmond, California (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Treviño, Daniel, killing, San Jose (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - United Farm Workers of Texas (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Zimbabwe, police brutality (Box 53, Folder 8)
- SERIES V: EPHEMERA, n.d.
  - CASA buttons (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Cloth banner, Pedro Albizu Campos (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Graphics (1) (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Graphics (2) (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Paste-up and lay-out sheets (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Plaque (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Rollo-dex address file (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - (For additional ephemera, see also the oversized materials listed at end of guide.) (Box 54, Folder *)
- SERIES VI: SOUND RECORDINGS, n.d.
  - Cassette tapes (Box 55)
- Series VII. Oversized Materials (Posters)
  - A call to action - Moratorium (Box OS, Folder 1)
  - Capitalismo-Negacion de los derechos humanos (Box OS, Folder 2)
  - Con o sin documentos-somos trabajadores; tenemos derechos; hacemos la riquesa (Box OS, Folder 3)
  - Jornada de solidaridad con los trabajadores Mexicanos en los Estados Unidos (sindicato de Trabajadores del Infonavit) (Box OS, Folder 4)
  - Libertad a Ismael Gonzalez, Preso Politico (Box OS, Folder 5)
  - Marcha contra la ley Rodino (Box OS, Folder 6)
  - Marcha contra la migra (Box OS, Folder 7)
  - National Chicano-Latino Conference on Immigration and Public Policy (Box OS, Folder 8)
  - National Moratorium Against Repression and Deportation (Box OS, Folder 9)
  - Resistencia Rally, Salazar Park (Box OS, Folder 10)